Sign In My Account

[HOME](https://www.fibro.org/) SERVICES [OUR ROOTS](https://www.fibro.org/our-roots) [WHAT IS FIBROMYALGIA?](https://www.fibro.org/what-is-fibromyalgia) FIBRO CORNER Voices of Fibro [Community PAGE](https://www.fibro.org/empowerment-groups) [Sponsors and Partners](https://www.fibro.org/sponsors-and-partners) [FIBRO YOUTH ADVOCATES](https://www.fibro.org/fibro-youth-advocates) EVENTS [BOARD OF TRUSTEES](https://www.fibro.org/board-of-trustees) [CONTACT](https://www.fibro.org/contact) [VOLUNTEER](https://www.fibro.org/volunteer)

Back [SERVICES](https://www.fibro.org/services-1) [Virtual COE Program](https://www.fibro.org/virtual-coe-program) [EMERGENCY ASSISTANCE INFO](https://www.fibro.org/fibrocaresservicesinfo) [Nutrition/Fresh Food](https://www.fibro.org/nutrition) [Fibro Warrior Scholarship](https://www.fibro.org/scholarship)

Back [MI VOZ English blog](https://www.fibro.org/mi-voz) [Mi VOZ-en Espanol blog](https://www.fibro.org/mi-vozenespanol) [Fibro Focused](https://www.fibro.org/fibro-focused) [Enfocados En Fibro](https://www.fibro.org/enfocados-en-fibro) [Press & Media](https://www.fibro.org/press-media)

Back [VOICES OF FIBRO](https://www.fibro.org/voicesoffibro) [VOICES OF FIBRO BOOK](https://www.fibro.org/voices-of-fibro-book) [VOICES OF FIBRO STORIES](https://www.fibro.org/voices-of-fibrostories) [VOICES Personal BLOG](https://www.fibro.org/blog-1) [VOICES POETRY-ODE TO FIBRO](https://www.fibro.org/ode-to-fibro)

Back [FCSA Events](https://www.fibro.org/fcsa-events) [Mariposa 2018](https://www.fibro.org/mariposa2018) [Mariposa 2019](https://www.fibro.org/mariposa2019) [Mariposa 2021](https://www.fibro.org/mariposa2021) [Caterpillar Walk 2018](https://www.fibro.org/caterpillar-walk-2018) [Caterpillar Run 2018](https://www.fibro.org/caterpillar-run-2018) [Caterpillar Walk Events 2022](https://www.fibro.org/caterpillar-walk-events-2022) [Caterpillar Walk 2019](https://www.fibro.org/caterpillar-walk-2019) [Caterpillar Run 2019](https://www.fibro.org/caterpillar-run-2019) [Caterpillar Walk Events 2020](https://www.fibro.org/2020-caterpillar-walk-events) [Caterpillar Walk/Run 2021](https://www.fibro.org/caterpillarwalk2021) [NYC Caterpillar Walk 2023](https://www.fibro.org/fibromyalgiawalk)

Sign In My Account

REVOLUTIONIZING FIBROMYALGIA CARE

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Last Updated:  12/24/2021

Fibromyalgia Care Society of America (“FCSA”) shares your concerns about the privacy of personal information collected on the internet and through telehealth services.  The following privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) is intended to explain how we collect and use information in connection with our website located at [www.fibro.org](http://www.fibro.org/) (“Site”) and our telehealth  services (“Telehealth Services”) (the Site and the Telehealth Services are collectively “Services”).  Your use of the Site is subject to the provisions of this Privacy Policy as well as those of our [Site Terms of Use,](https://www.fibro.org/termsofuse) and your use of any of the Telehealth Services is subject to the provisions of this Privacy Policy as well as those of our [Telehealth Terms of Use.](https://www.fibro.org/telehealthtermsofuse)   

Please note that we may revise our Privacy Policy at any time.  We encourage you to periodically visit this page to review our most current Privacy Policy.  Your continued use of any of our Site shall constitute your acceptance of any such changes to our Privacy Policy.

By using our Services, you agree that your personal information will be handled as described in this Privacy Policy.  Your use of the Services, and any dispute over privacy, is subject to this policy and our Site Terms of Service and our Telehealth Terms of Service, including their limitation on damages and resolution of disputes.  The [Site Terms of Use](https://www.fibro.org/termsofuse) and the [Telehealth Terms of Use](https://www.fibro.org/telehealthtermsofuse) are each incorporated by reference into this policy.

1.     WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU AND WHY?

We may collect information about you directly from you and from third parties, as well as automatically through your use of our Site or Services.

A.     INFORMATION THAT YOU PROVIDE TO US

During Registration:  You may use our Site without registration, but you must register with us to use our Telehealth Services.  To register, you must provide certain information, such as your name, date of birth, gender, address, mailing address, email, mobile and work phone, as well as a user ID and password.  We may also collect certain optional information, such as middle name or initial, home phone, and other contact information.  We may also collect your social security number and driver’s license information, other demographic information, credit card number and billing details, pictures and communications preferences.

Assessments and Surveys: We will collect information about you in our assessments and surveys, which include information your physical, behavioral and mental health history, diagnoses, and goals.  

During Visit.  In addition, you may communicate other personal information to a FCSA Consultant during a telehealth visit that may be entered into our records about you. 

Other.  We also collect other information that you submit on our Site, such as comments and blog postings (see “User Generated Content” section below).  You must submit your name to post a comment to our blog and you may submit other optional information as well.

B.     INFORMATION WE AUTOMATICALLY COLLECT ABOUT YOU

We may automatically collect the following information about your use of our Site or Services through cookies, web beacons, and other technologies: your domain name; your browser type and operating system; web pages you view; links you click; your IP address; a time and date stamp and the length of time you visit our Site and or use our Services; the referring URL, or the webpage that led you to our Site; and your browser type. We may combine this information with other information that we have collected about you, including, where applicable, your username, name, and other personal information. Please see the section “Our Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Mechanisms” below for more information about our use of cookies and other tracking mechanisms.

2.     HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

 We use the information that we gather about you for the following purposes:

·       To provide our Services.

·       To communicate with you about your use of our Services, to respond to your inquiries, to provide technical support and assistance and for other customer service purposes.

·       To communicate with you regarding the availability of Services on behalf of your FCSA Consultant , otherwise, we do not market to Consumers.

·       To send you reminders and other information related to your care on behalf of your FCSA Consultant.

·       To tailor the content and information that we may send or display, to offer location customization, and personalized help and instructions, and to otherwise personalize your experiences while using the Site or our Services.

·       To send offers and other promotional communications to FCSA Consultants;

·       To display advertising on our Site.

·       To better understand how users’ access and use our Services, both on an aggregated and individualized basis, in order to improve our Site and Services and respond to user desires and preferences, and for other research and analytical purposes.

3.     HOW WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION

We may share the information that we collect about you, including personally identifiable information, as follows:

·       FCSA Consultants. Your information will be shared with FCSA Consultants as directed and consented to by you. Our Services make your Assessments and related information available to your FCSA Consultant.   If you have questions regarding how the FCSA Consultant will use your personal information, please ask the FCSA Consultant for a copy of their Notice of Privacy Practices.

·       Service Providers. We may disclose the information we collect from you to third party vendors, service providers, contractors or agents who perform functions on our behalf.

·       Business Transfers. If we are acquired by or merged with another company, if substantially all of our assets are transferred to another company, or if we are a part of a bankruptcy proceeding, we may transfer the information we have collected from you to the other Company.

·       In Response to Legal Process. We also may disclose the information we collect from you in order to comply with the law, a judicial proceeding, court order, or other legal process, such as in response to a subpoena in compliance with applicable privacy laws.

·       To Protect Us and Others. We also may disclose the information we collect from you to the extent permitted by law, where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Use or this Policy, or as evidence in litigation in which FCSA is involved.

·       Aggregate and De-Identified Information. We may share aggregate or de-identified information about users with third parties for marketing, advertising, research or similar purposes.

4.     OUR USE OF COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING MECHANISMS

We use cookies and other tracking mechanisms to track information about your use of our Site or Services. We may combine this information with other information we collect from you.

Cookies.  Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser for record-keeping purposes. Some cookies allow us to make it easier for you to navigate our Site and Services, while others are used to enable a faster log-in process or to allow us to track your activities at our Site and Service.  Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can edit your browser options to block them in the future.  Visitors to our Site who disable cookies will be able to browse public areas of the Site, but the Telehealth Services may not function.

Clear GIFs (a.k.a. web beacons, web bugs or pixel tags).  Clear GIFs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on your computer’s hard drive, clear GIFs are embedded invisibly on web pages. We may use clear GIFs (in connection with our Site to, among other things, track the activities of Site visitors, help us manage content, and compile statistics about Site usage. We and our third-party service providers also use clear GIFs in HTML e-mails to our customers, to help us track e-mail response rates, identify when our e-mails are viewed, and track whether our e-mails are forwarded.

Third Party Analytics. We use automated devices and applications, such as [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html?rd=1), to evaluate usage of our Site and Services and to help us personalize content on out Site and Services. We also may use other analytic means to evaluate our Services. We use these tools to help us improve our Services, performance and user experiences. These entities may use cookies and other tracking technologies to perform their services. We do not share your personal information with these third parties.

Advertising. We may use network advertisers, such as [AdRoll](https://www.adroll.com/about/privacy), to advertise our Site and Services on other Sites, and we may do so based on your visits to our Site and to other third-party Sites. These entities may use cookies and other tracking technologies to perform their services. We do not share your personal information with these third parties.  Our Site does not currently respond to browser “Do-Not-Track requests; however, you may find out more about targeted advertising in general, and opt out of targeted ads from many ad networks, including AdRoll, through the National Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) [Site](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/), or the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) [Site](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).

5.     USER GENERATED CONTENT

We may invite you to post content on our Site, including your comments.  FCSA cannot prevent such information from being used in a manner that may violate this Policy, the law, or your personal privacy.  As a result, you should never post any sensitive information to our Site that you are not comfortable sharing publicly (e.g., personal medical details).  FCSA is not liable to you or any other person for any content or information you post to our Site or the use or disclosure of such content or information by other users or third parties.

We may also invite you to participate in various group meetings with other FSCA registrants (“Community Circles”), which may be held remotely through our Services.   Although our expectation is that participants will keep the identities of participants and disclosures of information confidential, FCSA cannot prevent other participants from using information in a way that may violate this Policy, the law, or your personal privacy. FCSA is not liable to you or any other person for any information you disclose in the Community Circles or information by other users or third parties.

6.     ACCESS TO MY PERSONAL INFORMATION 

You may modify registration information that you have submitted by logging into your account and updating your profile information. Please note that copies of information that you have updated, modified or deleted may remain viewable in cached and archived pages of the Site for a period of time.

7.     SECURITY OF INFORMATION

The security of your personal information is one of our primary concerns, and we use a variety of safeguards to protect your information from unauthorized access.  Despite the use of these safeguards, however, we cannot guarantee and do not represent that your information will always be secure from unauthorized access.  Accordingly, FCSA and its shareholders, members, trustees, directors, officers, employees, agents, legal representatives, predecessors, successors and assigns are not responsible for the security of any information collected by FCSA or transmitted through the internet, and you assume the sole and complete risk for using the Site and must make your own determination about these matters. 

8.     LINKS TO THIRD PARTIES

Our Site may contain links to sites operated by or controlled by third parties, including for services that require the sharing of information collected by cookies.  We do not necessarily endorse these products and/or services.   These third parties may have separate and independent privacy policies, and FCSA and its shareholders, members, trustees, directors, officers, employees, agents, legal representatives, predecessors, successors and assigns are not responsible or liable for your use or linking to these third-party sites or any information transmitted between our Site and these sites, and you assume the sole and complete risk for using these sites and must make your own determination about these matters.

9.     CHILDREN

We do not knowingly collect information about children under the age of 13.  Children under the age of 13 should receive parental permission before disclosing any information. 

10.  CONTACT INFORMATION

FIBROMYALGIA CARE SOCIETY OF AMERICA (FCSA)

40 South Fullerton Avenue, Montclair, NJ 07042

Phone:  973-954-5647

Email:  [info@fibro.org](mailto:info@fibro.org)

© 2022 FIBROMYALGIA CARE SOCIETY OF AMERICA, INC.   All rights reserved.

Fibromyalgia Care Society of America, inc

40 South Fullerton Avenue, Suite 18,

Montclair,

United States

Hours

Mon Open

Tue Open

Wed Open

Thu Open

Fri Open

Privacy Policy

Enter your email below to stay up to date on the movement.

Email Address 

Sign Up

Thank you!
